// QuestionSet.js
export const quiz = {
    questions: [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: 'Which gender do you identify with?',
            answers: ['Female',
                'Male',
                'Non-binary',
                'Prefer not to answer'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },

        {
            id: 2,
            question: `Have you ever been diagnosed with Binge Eating Disorder (BED)?`,
            answers: ['I am diagnosed by a doctor.', 'I am self diagnosed.', 'I suspect I might have BED.', 'Not with BED, but another eating disorder.','Soomething else'],
            correctAnswer: 'JavaScript',
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            question: 'Do you feel in control of how much you eat?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely'],
            correctAnswer: 'Querying databases',
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question: 'Do you eat meals much more quickly than others and seem to eat a lot more than others as well?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Model View Controller',
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            question: 'Do you have a strong habit of eating when you are bored such that nothing else can distract you?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            question: 'Do you often feel desperate that you cannot be more in control of what you eat?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            question: 'Do you often eat, even though you are not hungry, because of habit?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            question: 'Is it easy for you to get back on track with a diet or healthy regime?',
            answers: ['Yes','No'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 9,
            question: 'Do you sometimes make youtself sick because you are so uncomfortably full?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 10,
            question: 'Does your life seem to be feast or famine with very little moderation?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 11,
            question: 'Do you tend to eat all day with no defined meal times?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 12,
            question: 'Do you eat about the same amount of food every day and rarely binge?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 13,
            question: 'Do you relate to the following statement?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','4','5'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 14,
            question: 'Do you relate to the following statement?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','4','5'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 15,
            question: 'Do you have strong feelings of self-hate or guilt if you overeat?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 16,
            question: 'Are you your harshest critic?',
            answers: ['Yes','No'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 17,
            question: 'Do you feel self-conscious eating around other people?',
            answers: ['Yes','No'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 18,
            question: 'How frequently do you eat as a way to cope with difficult emotions?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 19,
            question: 'Do you feel very self-conscious about your weight and body size such that it stops you from socializing?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 20,
            question: 'Do you notice that you reach for certain types of food (e.g., sweets, comfort foods) when you are feeling emotionally upset?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time',
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 21,
            question: 'How often do you find yourself thinking about your body image?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 22,
            question: 'Do you usually not know how physically hungry you really are and eat more than you need?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface', //Has a tip page after this one
        },
        {
            id: 23,
            question: 'How often do you get distracted by thoughts about food when trying to focus?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 24,
            question: 'How often do you experience difficulty falling asleep or staying asleep after a binge eating episode?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 25,
            question: 'How often do you skip meals?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 26,
            question: 'Have you heard of Alexithymia?',
            answers: ['Yes','No'], //These are emojis on the Figma file
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface', //Comes with two more screens of yes or no
        },
        {
            id: 27,
            question: 'How strong is your knowledge of binge eating?',
            answers: ['I know very little about binge eating.', 'I know the basics, but that is about it.', 
                'I have a good understanding.', 'I am an expert in all things binge eating'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 28,
            question: 'When did you first suspect you might be dealing with a binge eating issue?',
            answers: ['<6 months ago', '6 months - 1 year ago', 
                '1-2 years ago', 'More than 2 years ago'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 29,
            question: 'Do you suspect you have any other mental health conditions that impact your life?',
            answers: ['Anxiety', 'Depression', 
                'Alcohol / Substance Use', 'Body Dismorphia', 'Other', 'None'],
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 30,
            question: 'Do you relate to following statement?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 31,
            question: 'Do you relate to following statement?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
        {
            id: 32,
            question: 'Do you relate to following statement?',
            answers: ['All the time', 'A lot of the time', 
                'Sometimes', 'Rarely', 'Never'], //These are emojis
            correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        },
    ],
};